<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Secure Delivery</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/</link><description>Recent content on Secure Delivery</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 11:30:08 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://securedelivery.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Securing the Digital Factory: Part 1</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/articles/securing-the-digital-factory-part-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 11:30:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/articles/securing-the-digital-factory-part-1/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what&amp;rsquo;s the best hero image for an article talking about &amp;ldquo;digital factories&amp;rdquo;, maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;Minority Report but in a hardhat&amp;rdquo; kind of vibe? Let&amp;rsquo;s go with that. To business!
If you know me you know I&amp;rsquo;m not a big fan of analogies. They&amp;rsquo;re generally used to poorly convey a reasonably complex topic in an overly-simplistic way, by people who have a poor understanding of the subject matter to start with.</description></item><item><title>Modern Slavery and Human Trafficking Policy Statement</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/modern-slavery-and-human-trafficking-policy-statement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 10:50:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/modern-slavery-and-human-trafficking-policy-statement/</guid><description>1. Introduction Modern Slavery is an indefensible violation of basic human rights and Secure Delivery recognises we have a moral responsibility to prevent slavery and human trafficking in our business activities and to require our supply chain to do the same.
We only seek to engage with reputable organisations and are keen to work with our employees, partners, associates and end clients to do whatever we can to help eradicate this practice in the United Kingdom.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 10:50:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/privacy-policy/</guid><description>This website is operated by Secure Delivery Ltd and whose registered address is Office 7, 35/37 Ludgate Hill, London, EC4M 7JN. We are committed to protecting and preserving the privacy of our visitors when visiting our site or communicating electronically with us.
This policy sets out how we process any personal data we collect from you or that you provide to us through our website. We confirm that we will keep your information secure and that we will comply fully with all applicable UK Data Protection legislation and regulations.</description></item><item><title>OWASP API Top 10 CTF Walk-through</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/articles/api-top-ten-walkthrough/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/articles/api-top-ten-walkthrough/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been promising this walk-through for a while now (ever since first updating this material to use the awesome vAPI CTF 1.1) and now I&amp;rsquo;ve finally gotten around to it.
Getting started To get started with you&amp;rsquo;ll need to have access to the following tools: Docker - please ensure that you can use docker-compose; git - please make sure you can git clone public repositories; Postman; and of course ZAP.</description></item><item><title>Foundations of Product Security for Decision Makers</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/training/foundations-of-product-security-for-decision-makers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/training/foundations-of-product-security-for-decision-makers/</guid><description>Product owners, project managers, business analysts, architects - all the people that connect your products to business value and customer requirements are critical to the security of what you&amp;rsquo;re delivering. The day-to-day decision makers make a huge contribution to prioritisation of work and the quality of the delivered product.
This foundational workshop gives all decision-makers an understanding of where security sits alongside overall product quality, what must be measured to inform their decision making around security, and how to implement the simple but powerful processes that keep security and overall product quality under control while delivering at pace.</description></item><item><title>Secure by Design With Agile Threat Modelling</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/training/secure-by-design-with-agile-threat-modelling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/training/secure-by-design-with-agile-threat-modelling/</guid><description>Threat modelling is an essential part of building secure systems. The United States’ Executive Order 14028 to improve the nation’s cybersecurity mandates threat modeling as part of the minimum standard for verification. OWASP’s Top 10:2021 puts Insecure Design at number 4 of the top 10 risks to businesses.
To scale threat modelling to cover your whole organisation you must put the capability into the hands of of your product development teams.</description></item><item><title>Secure Delivery Announces New Partnership with Snyk</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/press-releases/secure-delivery-announces-new-partnership-with-snyk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 11:22:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/press-releases/secure-delivery-announces-new-partnership-with-snyk/</guid><description>London — December 7, 2021. Secure Delivery today announced its channel partnership with Snyk, the leader in developer security. The new partnership will combine Snyk’s leading developer security tooling with Secure Delivery’s proven security coaching, consulting and managed services to accelerate the vigour of security capabilities in digital delivery organisations worldwide.
People, process and technology are at the heart of any scalable security transformation and focussing on all three will elevate an organisation to world-class security capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Chesterton's Fence, and Monkeys</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/articles/chestertons-fence-and-monkeys/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 08:14:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/articles/chestertons-fence-and-monkeys/</guid><description>Chesterton&amp;rsquo;s Fence, and Monkeys G. K. Chesterton—writer; modernist philosopher; friend to George Bernard Shaw, H. G. Wells and Bertrand Russell but, most importantly, author of a piece I can torture into an article on security.
Chesterton&amp;rsquo;s fence In the matter of reforming things, as distinct from deforming them, there is one plain and simple principle; a principle which will probably be called a paradox. There exists in such a case a certain institution or law; let us say, for the sake of simplicity, a fence or gate erected across a road.</description></item><item><title>How to Scale Product Security Across the ORg</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/articles/how-to-scale-product-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 13:29:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/articles/how-to-scale-product-security/</guid><description>The Ratio In our work with large organisations we&amp;rsquo;ve developed a &amp;ldquo;rule of thumb&amp;rdquo; that quite usefully predicts the proportion of development and cybersecurity staff in the workforce. For companies whose primary business isn&amp;rsquo;t software development but have internal, established application delivery capability (banks, telcos, etc.) around 10% of the workforce are software developers.
At the scale these organisations operate at, typically an architecture function has split off from engineering and is around 10% of the developer total.</description></item><item><title>What is The Cloud? (it's Zero Trust)</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/articles/what-is-the-cloud-its-zero-trust/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 11:37:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/articles/what-is-the-cloud-its-zero-trust/</guid><description>Is this guy really going to do a “What is the cloud?” article in 2020? Yes, he is. I mean, I am. Because I want to talk about the cloud. No, not cloud computing. No, not a series of tubes. Not &amp;ldquo;just someone else&amp;rsquo;s computer&amp;rdquo;. This cloud:
This actual cloud. We’ve all seen it thousands of times, and you&amp;rsquo;ve probably used it a lot if you’re reading this article. You might have seen it in use like:</description></item><item><title>The Chaos Butterfly of Security Standards</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/articles/the-chaos-butterfly-of-security-standards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 09:32:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/articles/the-chaos-butterfly-of-security-standards/</guid><description>The mathematician and meteorologist, Edward Lorenz, made the Butterfly Effect famous with his talk in 1972, &amp;ldquo;Does the Flap of a Butterfly&amp;rsquo;s Wings in Brazil Set Off a Tornado in Texas?&amp;rdquo; and it&amp;rsquo;s stuck in the popular conscious ever since. The notion that small events in a chaotic system can build to large changes over time and space.
In large companies I frequently see a hope that a similar mechanism will occur when a security standard is published to the company SharePoint.</description></item><item><title>The Biggest Misconception in Application Security</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/articles/biggest-misconception-in-appsec/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 09:41:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/articles/biggest-misconception-in-appsec/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve touched on this in previous articles, but it&amp;rsquo;s worth dedicating a little time to this misconception as it&amp;rsquo;s at the root of so many of the problems that organisations have with security and delivery. A common way to think about maintaining security while delivering software systems at pace is this.
Where rapid delivery of changes into production is one end of a scale, being secure is at the other end and, as an organisation, you pick where along the scale you&amp;rsquo;re comfortable according to your risk appetite.</description></item><item><title>Building a Culture of Quality, Not Just Security</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/articles/building-a-culture-of-quality-not-just-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 08:30:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/articles/building-a-culture-of-quality-not-just-security/</guid><description>In my previous article I covered how security is just one aspect of the quality of the applications you&amp;rsquo;re building. Today I&amp;rsquo;d like to focus on the process of building high quality systems and, in a startling break with tradition, actually define what culture is so that we can talk meaningfully about culture change.
Let&amp;rsquo;s remind ourselves of the standard for software quality from ISO 25010:
It never makes sense to talk about &amp;ldquo;building a culture of security&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Number of Data Breaches is not a Good Security Metric</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/articles/number-of-data-breaches-is-not-a-good-security-metric/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 11:30:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/articles/number-of-data-breaches-is-not-a-good-security-metric/</guid><description>Ok, of course it&amp;rsquo;s not. Does this feel familiar though?
Budget gets allocated to cybersecurity Cybersecurity activities happen Everyone is reasonably happy, except the application delivery teams having cybersecurity activities done to them Terrible news - a data breach! PANIC Budget gets substantially increased for cybersecurity Substantially more cybersecurity activities happen Everyone is reasonably happy, except the application delivery teams having substantially more cybersecurity activities done to them Terrible news - a data breach!</description></item></channel></rss>