<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Workshops on Secure Delivery</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/workshops/</link><description>Recent content in Workshops on Secure Delivery</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 07:53:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://securedelivery.io/workshops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Secure Coding Techniques &amp; Practices</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/workshops/secure-coding-techniques-and-practices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 07:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/workshops/secure-coding-techniques-and-practices/</guid><description>Security defects in code are the largest contributor to security vulnerabilities in software systems. A NIST study in 2016 established that a programming defect was the root cause of 73% of all reported software system vulnerabilities tracked in the CVE database from 2008-2016.
Everyone who is hands-on with code at your organisation must know how to program securely to avoid the mistakes that we see over and over again at organisations around the world.</description></item><item><title>Foundations of Product Security for Decision Makers</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/workshops/foundations-of-product-security-for-decision-makers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/workshops/foundations-of-product-security-for-decision-makers/</guid><description>Product owners, project managers, business analysts, architects - all the people that connect your products to business value and customer requirements are critical to the security of what you&amp;rsquo;re delivering. The day-to-day decision makers make a huge contribution to prioritisation of work and the quality of the delivered product.
This foundational workshop gives all decision-makers an understanding of where security sits alongside overall product quality, what must be measured to inform their decision making around security, and how to implement the simple but powerful processes that keep security and overall product quality under control while delivering at pace.</description></item><item><title>Secure by Design With Agile Threat Modelling</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/workshops/secure-by-design-with-agile-threat-modelling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/workshops/secure-by-design-with-agile-threat-modelling/</guid><description>Threat modelling is an essential part of building secure systems. The United States’ Executive Order 14028 to improve the nation’s cybersecurity mandates threat modeling as part of the minimum standard for verification. OWASP’s Top 10:2021 puts Insecure Design at number 4 of the top 10 risks to businesses.
To scale threat modelling to cover your whole organisation you must put the capability into the hands of of your product development teams.</description></item></channel></rss>