<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Practioners on Secure Delivery</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/practioners/</link><description>Recent content in Practioners on Secure Delivery</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 21:53:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://securedelivery.io/practioners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chris Wood</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/practioners/chris-wood/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/practioners/chris-wood/</guid><description>Waiting for Chris&amp;rsquo;s bio&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Derek Panton</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/practioners/derek-panton/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/practioners/derek-panton/</guid><description>Derek is a Senior Cyber security strategist with a track record of delivering advanced cyber security technologies and solutions across diverse industry sectors.
Previous lead roles with Accenture, PWC, CA, IBM, Unilever, GSK, Reckitt Benckiser, Astra Zeneca; leading the development of innovative security strategies to improve operational effectiveness, maximize investments for Fortune 100 companies as well as having worked on national healthcare projects. He worked on the rationalization strategy for Vodafone customer Cloud and business hosting solutions, PWC’s Identity and Access Management employee and client engagement platform, UK NHS Spine which joins together over 23,000 healthcare IT systems in 20,500 organisations.</description></item><item><title>Vee Schmitt</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/practioners/vee-schmitt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/practioners/vee-schmitt/</guid><description>Veronica started her forensic career in 2008. Veronica is also an Assistant Professor at Noroff University. Veronica holds a Master in Science at Rhodes University in Information Security with specialisation in the forensic analysis of malware. She prides herself in keeping patients safe as this is something which is near to her heart. She is also a cyborg sporting an embedded medical device herself. She also is a DEF CON Goon and she is the founder of DC2751, and the OWASP Kristiansand project.</description></item></channel></rss>