<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Practitioners on Secure Delivery</title><link>https://securedelivery.io/practitioners/</link><description>Recent content in Practitioners on Secure Delivery</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 14:38:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://securedelivery.io/practitioners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://securedelivery.io/practitioners/chris-wood/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/practitioners/chris-wood/</guid><description>Chris is a highly experienced technologist specialising in APIs and a subject matter expert on Open Banking.
He has expert knowledge on APIs, including API design and developer experience, and security protocols like OpenID Connect and FIDO2/Webauthn. His Open Banking knowledge comes from real-world experience. Chris was part of the HSBC team that helped deliver the first releases of the UK Open Banking Standards and also worked with the Open Banking Implementation Entity as an API architect and standards co-author.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://securedelivery.io/practitioners/derek-panton/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/practitioners/derek-panton/</guid><description>Derek is a Senior Cyber security strategist with a track record of delivering advanced cyber security technologies and solutions across diverse industry sectors.
Previous lead roles with Accenture, PWC, CA, IBM, Unilever, GSK, Reckitt Benckiser, Astra Zeneca; leading the development of innovative security strategies to improve operational effectiveness, maximize investments for Fortune 100 companies as well as having worked on national healthcare projects. He worked on the rationalization strategy for Vodafone customer Cloud and business hosting solutions, PWC’s Identity and Access Management employee and client engagement platform, UK NHS Spine which joins together over 23,000 healthcare IT systems in 20,500 organisations.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://securedelivery.io/practitioners/grant-ongers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/practitioners/grant-ongers/</guid><description>Grant is the CTO and one of the co-founders of Secure Delivery. He&amp;rsquo;s an experienced CISO, with experience spanning development, operations and security. He&amp;rsquo;s built platforms for regulated industries for more than 10 years, has over 20 years managing operations from NOCs to mainframe and DBs. He also has over 30 years pushing the limits of (Info)Sec—mostly white-hat.
Grant’s community involvement is global, he is:
Staff at BSides (London, Las Vegas, and Cape Town) Goon at DEF CON (USA) for nearly ten years and DC2721 co-founder Staff at BlackHat (USA and EU) Grant has sat on the OWASP® Foundation&amp;rsquo;s global board of directors OWASP for the last two years.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://securedelivery.io/practitioners/vee-schmidt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/practitioners/vee-schmidt/</guid><description>Veronica started her forensic career in 2008. Veronica is also an Assistant Professor at Noroff University. Veronica holds a Master in Science at Rhodes University in Information Security with specialisation in the forensic analysis of malware. She prides herself in keeping patients safe as this is something which is near to her heart. She is also a cyborg sporting an embedded medical device herself. She also is a DEF CON Goon and she is the founder of DC2751, and the OWASP Kristiansand project.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://securedelivery.io/practitioners/toby-irvine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://securedelivery.io/practitioners/toby-irvine/</guid><description>Toby is the CEO and one of the co-founders of Secure Delivery. He has spent (well) over 20 years in secure software engineering, designing and building large scale on-premise and cloud systems across many industries. He&amp;rsquo;s established &amp;amp; managed secure engineering and security engineering functions in highly regulated organisations.
He&amp;rsquo;s trained technical and non-technical delivery roles across the Americas, EMEA and APAC in modern application security practices and founded Secure Delivery to bring both strategic advisory and proven training in modern application security thinking, practices and tooling to regulated organisations.</description></item></channel></rss>